♪I lament on the cruel and untimely love♪
أنا أتحسر على الحب القاسي والغير أوانه ♪
♪Yet I come to realise it's a daydream when the bubbles burst♪
♪ ومع ذلك أدركت أنه حلم يقظة عندما تنفجر الفقاعات ♪
♪A city of spring flowers♪
♪ مدينة زهور الربيع ♪
♪Sinks into the indifferent autumnal frost♪
♪ يغرق في الصقيع الخريفي غير المبال
♪A snowflake falls into the river♪
♪ تسقط ندفة ثلجية في النهر ♪
♪The biting cold stalks over♪
♪ السيقان الباردة القارضة
♪All assumptions are nothing♪
كل الافتراضات لا شيء
♪But a disguised makeup♪
♪ لكن مكياج مقنع
♪I bid farewell♪
أودع
♪To the passionate gaze behind the mask♪
♪ للنظرة العاطفية خلف القناع ♪
♪Love and hate are the most unforgettable feelings♪
الحب والكراهية من أكثر المشاعر التي لا تنسى
♪Overwhelmed by my longings♪
غارقة في شوقي ♪
♪I tear off those old scores♪
♪ مزقت تلك الدرجات القديمة ♪
♪I bid farewell♪
أودع
♪To the irretrievable past♪
إلى الماضي الذي لا يمكن استرجاعه ♪
=Little Mad Doctor=
= الطبيب المجنون الصغير =
=Episode 12=
= الحلقة 12 =
My Lord.
ربي.
This is your favourite sweet corn with pine nuts.
هذه هي الذرة الحلوة المفضلة لديك مع الصنوبر.
Do you know the cousin sister of Ye Feibai?
هل تعرف أخت ابنة عم يي فيباي؟
I can't recall her name.
لا استطيع تذكر اسمها.
Oh, right.
صحيح.
It's Ming Bao'er.
إنه مينغ باوير.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Why do you ask about her?
لماذا تسأل عنها؟
Well.
حسنًا.
Nothing. I'm just curious.
لا شئ.  أنا مجرد فضول.
His cousin seems
يبدو ابن عمه
to have great interest in him.
ليهتم به كثيرًا.
I wonder what he thinks about her.
أتساءل ما الذي يعتقده عنها.
He doesn't have any interest in her.
ليس لديه أي اهتمام بها.
How do you know?
كيف علمت بذلك؟
I think Ye Feibai
أعتقد يي فيباي
deserves someone to treat him sincerely.
يستحق من يعامله بصدق.
However, I think his cousin
ومع ذلك ، أعتقد أن ابن عمه
doesn't suit him.
لا يناسبه.
If so,
لو ذلك،
what do you think of Ye Feibai,
ما رأيك في يي فيباي ،
Princess Jinghong?
الأميرة جينغهونغ؟
He's strong despite his crippled body.
إنه قوي بالرغم من جسده المعطل.
what do you think
ماذا تعتقد؟
about Ye Feibai
حول يي فيباي
and Lord War?
ولورد الحرب؟
Lord War is no doubt the best.
لا شك أن لعبة Lord War هي الأفضل.
The only best man.
أفضل رجل.
Ming Yueye.
مينغ يويي.
Ye Feibai.
يي فيباي.
Both their backgrounds
كلا خلفياتهم
are mysterious.
غامضة.
They appear
يظهرون
to have emerged from nowhere.
خرجت من العدم.
Emerged from nowhere?
خرجت من العدم؟
Ming Yueye also goes by another name,
Ming Yueye أيضًا يحمل اسمًا آخر ،
Ming Bao'er.
مينغ باوير.
You may leave.
يمكنك المغادرة.
Yes.
نعم.
Feibai
فيباي
is going to get married tomorrow?
هل سيتزوج غدا؟
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
The wedding gown and hair accessories for tomorrow are ready.
فستان الزفاف وإكسسوارات الشعر ليوم غد جاهزان.
I have asked someone to send them back to Suoqing Palace.
لقد طلبت من شخص ما أن يعيدهم إلى قصر Suoqing.
Huh?
هاه؟
Sent back to Suoqing Palace?
العودة إلى قصر Suoqing؟
Yes.
نعم.
Oh, right.
صحيح.
Will His Highness come to fetch me
هل سيأتي سموه ليأخذني
with a grandeur procession?
مع موكب عظمة؟
Certainly.
بالتأكيد.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Your wedding gown is done.
ثوب الزفاف الخاص بك قد انتهى.
Huh?
هاه؟
The servants delivered the gown to Suoqing Palace.
قام الخدم بتسليم الثوب إلى قصر Suoqing.
So, I went all the way to get them back.
لذلك ، ذهبت طوال الطريق لاستعادتهم.
Ling'er.
لينغ.
Your Highness will be fetched from Suoqing Palace.
سموك سيتم جلبه من قصر Suoqing.
Why did you take them back?
لماذا استعدتهم؟
It's fine.
لا بأس.
It's fine to get them back here.
من الجيد إعادتهم إلى هنا.
I shall see how my wedding gown looks like.
سأرى كيف يبدو ثوب زفافي.
Are you insane?
هل أنت مجنون؟
What has Chu Jinghong done
ما الذي فعله Chu Jinghong
to beguile you?
لتخدعك؟
I have reminded you several times
لقد ذكرتك عدة مرات
not to offend Uncle Thirteen
ألا يسيء إلى العم الثالث عشر
before your power is established.
قبل تأسيس قوتك.
Look
ينظر
what you've done.
ماذا فعلت.
Chu Jinghong should've belonged to me.
كان يجب أن يكون Chu Jinghong ملكًا لي.
She was my maidservant.
كانت جاريتي.
If you can't let me marry her,
إذا كنت لا تسمح لي بالزواج منها ،
can you please
من فضلك هل بامكانك
stop her marriage with Uncle Thirteen?
توقف زواجها مع العم الثالث عشر؟
I beg of you.
أتوسل لك.
Fengxing.
فينجكسينج.
Yes, Consort.
نعم ، رفيقة.
What?
ماذا؟
Consort?
القرين؟
I'm not married yet.
لست متزوجا بعد.
Tomorrow...
غداً...
To me,
إلي
you're the consort.
أنت القرين.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
where's His Highness?
اين سموه
His...
له...
His Highness went to Jiuzhen Restaurant
ذهب سموه إلى مطعم جيوزين
to attend some business.
لحضور بعض الأعمال.
He will be back soon.
سوف يعود قريبا
I see.
أرى.
Please tell him
أخبره من فضلك
that I return to Suoqing Palace first.
أن أعود إلى قصر Suoqing أولاً.
I will see him...
سأراه ...
tomorrow.
غداً.
His Highness
صاحب السمو
has already summoned me
استدعاني بالفعل
to escort you back.
لمرافقتك للعودة.
Tonight,
الليلة،
I will guard at Suoqing Palace
سأحرس قصر Suoqing
to make sure nothing will happen.
للتأكد من عدم حدوث شيء.
Tomorrow,
غداً،
someone will come
سيأتي شخص ما
to dress you up.
لتلبس لك.
My Lord.
ربي.
Miss wants to see you
الآنسة تريد رؤيتك
to speak about something important with you.
للتحدث عن شيء مهم معك.
I'm afraid
أنا خائف
it's about my wedding tomorrow.
إنه يتعلق بزفافي غدًا.
Fengxing.
فينجكسينج.
Head to Jiuzhen Restaurant.
توجه إلى مطعم Jiuzhen.
Yes.
نعم.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Oh.
أوه.
Nothing.
لا شئ.
I just
أنا فقط
want to see him now.
تريد رؤيته الآن.
I see.
أرى.
Feibai.
فيباي.
♪I sigh at my life♪
♪ أنا أتنهد في حياتي ♪
♪There's nowhere to anchor on shore♪
♪ لا يوجد مكان للرسو على الشاطئ
♪Nothing to cherish in the world♪
لا شيء نعتز به في العالم
♪Except for you♪
ما عداك ♪
♪The past we've been through retains♪
♪ الماضي الذي مررنا به
♪Even though time wears thin♪
على الرغم من أن الوقت يضعف ♪
♪The thought of being together lifelong♪
فكرة البقاء معًا مدى الحياة
♪Exists beyond time♪
موجود خارج الزمن ♪
♪All joys and sorrows♪
♪ كل افراح و احزان ♪
♪Reflect in your gentle gaze♪
انعكس في نظراتك اللطيفة
♪I will spend my life waiting♪
♪ سأقضي حياتي في الانتظار ♪
♪For the chance to be forever by your side♪
للحصول على فرصة أن تكون بجانبك إلى الأبد
♪Hair turns grey in one winter night♪
♪ يتحول لون الشعر إلى اللون الرمادي في ليلة شتاء ♪
♪The appearance remains in spite of the thick frost♪
المظهر يبقى بالرغم من الصقيع الكثيف
♪Time slips by in that dream-like world♪
♪ الوقت يمر في هذا العالم الذي يشبه الحلم
♪Life is always full of splendor♪
♪ الحياة دائما مليئة بالروعة
♪We part when the flowers fall♪
♪ نفترق عندما تسقط الأزهار
♪Desolate chills blow away several autumns♪
♪ قشعريرة مقفرة تهب عدة خريفات ♪
♪Eternal love is all I seek♪
الحب الأبدي هو كل ما أسعى إليه
♪Though the sweet dream fades at last♪
رغم أن الحلم الجميل يتلاشى أخيرًا ♪
♪I sigh at my life♪
♪ أنا أتنهد في حياتي ♪
♪There's nowhere to anchor on shore♪
♪ لا يوجد مكان للرسو على الشاطئ
♪Nothing to cherish in the world♪
لا شيء نعتز به في العالم
♪Except for you♪
ما عداك ♪
♪The past we've been through retains♪
♪ الماضي الذي مررنا به
♪Even though time wears thin♪
على الرغم من أن الوقت يضعف ♪
♪The thought of being together lifelong♪
فكرة البقاء معًا مدى الحياة
♪Exists beyond time♪
موجود خارج الزمن ♪
♪All joys and sorrows♪
♪ كل افراح و احزان ♪
♪Reflect in your gentle gaze♪
انعكس في نظراتك اللطيفة
♪I will spend my life waiting♪
♪ سأقضي حياتي في الانتظار ♪
♪For the chance to be forever by your side♪
للحصول على فرصة أن تكون بجانبك إلى الأبد